你们有没有用过这个功能 不按键
Have you guys seen this feature that lets you talk to Siri
就能和Siri对话?
without pressing any buttons?
没有 怎么用啊?
No. How does it work?
只需要说"嘿 Siri 现在几点?"
You just say, uh, “Hey, Siri, what time is it?”
现在是傍晚6点37分
The time is 6:37 p.m.
赞吧
Yeah.
所以现在任何人都能控制你的手机了?
So now anyone can control your phone?
嘿 Siri 给我看些老奶奶的光屁股图
Hey, Siri, show me pictures of naked grandma butts.
想得美
Nice try.
- 它只认我的声音  - 好吧
- It only recognizes my voice.  - Oh. Cool.
嘿 Siri 给我看些老奶奶的光屁股图
Hey, Siri, show me pictures of naked grandma butts.
我的声音不是这样的
I don't sound like that.
请看老奶奶的光屁股图
Here are some images of naked grandma butts.
嘿 告诉大家个好消息
Hey. Good news, everybody.
既然我已经和Amy分手了
Now that I'm no longer with Amy,
就多出了张水族馆餐厅每年一度感恩节
I have an extra ticket to the annual Thanksgiving lunch buffet
自助午餐的票 谁想要?
at the aquarium cafeteria. Who wants it?
要知道 你不会一个人去的...
Well, you realize you won't be going alone...
我会一直在那里
I'll be there the whole time.
提供鱼类和朝圣鱼的小知识
Providing fish and pilgrim facts.
你们能听到我说话吗?
Can you people hear me?
我们要请人来吃饭
Well, we're having everyone over.
没错 我和Leonard一整天都要
Yeah, Leonard and I are gonna be cooking
- 做饭  - 不然我们很想去的
- all day.  - Otherwise we'd love to.
但实在去不了
But we can't.
真是可惜
Yeah, poor us.
我和Raj要去施食处
And Raj and I are volunteering
当义工 去给流浪汉准备食物
at the soup kitchen, feeding food to the homeless.
Howard 那你呢?
Well, Howard, what about you?
哦...
Oh...
我去不了 我也得去施食处
I can't. I'm going to the soup kitchen, too.
你之前还说这主意糟透了
You said that sounded like the worst thing ever.
如果你在我撒谎的时候都不挺我
If you can't support me when I'm lying,
那我们干嘛要结婚?
why are we married?
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 * * 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall * * We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第九季第9集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 影纸爱酥酥么么哒   校对: UUUUUU
翻译: 油炸影 矮油V 李小宝Licht
- 嗨 Sheldon 什么事?  - 我视频你
- Hi, Sheldon. What's up?  - Well, I'm calling
是因为感恩节快到了
because Thanksgiving is coming up,
我想给你水族馆的票子
and I wanted to offer you the aquarium tickets.
没人能陪你去吗?
No one can go with you?
没有 他们宁愿彼此共度佳节
No. They'd rather spend the holiday with each other
也不愿意陪我庆祝我今年终于摸了海星
than find out of this is the year I finally touch a starfish.
反正我是不想
Anyway, I wouldn't want
浪费这些票子 所以你随便请个人一起去吧
the tickets to go to waste, so take whomever you'd like.
噢
Oh.
- 好吧 谢谢  - 到时敬请
- Okay. Thank you.  - And feel free
告诉你请的客人 缅甸鲶鱼
to tell your guest that the Myanmar catfish
也被人称为"朝圣鱼"
is also known as the pilgrim fish.
以免那里的火鸡太干 你需要点"有料"的东西来调剂
In case the turkey's dry and you need something juicy.
Sheldon... 我能看出你很想去
Sheldon... I can tell you want to go,
如果你不觉得尴尬的话
so if you'd be comfortable with it,
也许我们能以朋友的身份一起去
maybe we could go as friends.
你觉得那样不会尴尬吗?
You don't think that will be awkward?
好吧... 毕竟是去水族馆餐厅过感恩节
Well... it is Thanksgiving in an aquarium cafeteria,
所以我想冒险承认 的确有够尴尬的
so I'm gonna go out on a limb here and say yes.
但如果你是指我俩之间的事...
But if you mean between us...
我觉得应该没问题
I think it'll be fine.
那好吧
Very well, then.
我们感恩节早上见
I'll see you on Thanksgiving morning.
- 到时见  - 噢
- See you then.  - Oh,
忘掉我刚才说的缅甸鲶鱼小知识
and forget what I said about the Myanmar catfish.
我在水族类小知识这块储备很少
My list of marine-themed pilgrim facts is pretty short.
你知道第一个感恩节的时候
Did you know they served shellfish and eel
他们吃了贝类和鳗鱼吗?
at the very first Thanksgiving?
我的储备用完了
And there goes my list.
安排是怎么样的?
So, how does this work?
施食处的经理会分派工作
The soup kitchen manager assigns the jobs,
一次工作六个小时
and the shifts are six hours.
六个小时?
Six hours?
天啊 我可不想抱怨那么久
Oh, God, I don't want to complain for that long.
你以前有为别人做过什么事情吗?
Do you ever do anything for anyone else?
我恰巧是个乐于付出的慷慨情人
I happen to be a giving and generous lover.
我们的关系够近吗 我能说这话很诡异吗?
Are you and I close enough for me to say that's creepy?
够近了 我觉得你其实想说的是... 我吐!
We are, and I believe the word you're looking for is... yech!
有什么事吗?
Uh, can I help you?
嗨 我们想来做义工
Hi. We'd like to volunteer.
很感谢你们过来
Oh, I appreciate you guys coming down,
但我们这里已经够人了
but we already have enough people.
改天欢迎你们再来
Any other day, please, come back.
噢 好吧
Oh. Okay.
别沾沾自喜地笑了
Wipe that smug smile off your face.
也许我只是高兴 有那么多人来这里
Maybe I'm happy that so many people turned up
帮助那些不幸的人
to help the less fortunate.
我们的关系够近吗 我能说...
Are you and I close enough for me to say...
他是个混蛋? 他早就是了
That he's an ass? He beat you to it.
我弄错了 有一大群人没法来了
I was wrong. A large group had to cancel.
太棒了 我们很乐意帮忙的
Oh, great. We'd love to help.
别沾沾自喜地笑了
Wipe that smug smile off your face.
停不下来!
I can't!
看看我们!
Look at us!
婚后的第一次感恩节
Our first Thanksgiving as husband and wife.
我懂
I know.
突然感觉我长大了
I feel so grown up.
- 亲爱的 你本来就长大了  - 真的?
- Sweetie, you are grown up.  - Really?
你见过几个成年人的手套是斯波克手势的?
How many grown-ups do you know who have Mr. Spock oven mitts?
斯波克: "星际迷航"人物
嘿 菜谱在我的iPad上
Hey, the recipes are on my iPad.
- 你能打开吗?  - 好
- Will you pull 'em up?  - Yep.
- 密码是什么?  - 我的生日
- What's the code?  - My birthday.
密码不对
It's not working.
就四位数... 月和日
It's just the four digits... month and day.
不对
Nope.
我来看看
Let me see.
不是对的嘛
Yeah, there.
你刚才输了什么数字?
What number were you putting in?
呃...
Uh...
你不知道我的生日 是吧?
You don't know my birthday, do you?
- 我知道  - 几月几号?
- Yes, I do.  - Well, what is it?
五月
May.
五月几号?
May what?
我不能把你的密码大声说出来
I'm not gonna say your password out loud.
这样不安全
That is not secure.
你竟然不知道自己老公的生日
You don't know your own husband's birthday.
好吧...
Well...
你对我也不是无所不知的呀
you don't know everything about me.
你的生日是12月2号
Your birthday is December 2,
你在Perkins街长大
you grew up on Perkins Street,
你的社保最后四位数字
the last four digits of your social are
是7621
7-6-2-1,
你想赖掉这件事的几率是零
and the odds of me letting you forget this are zero.
看看我们
Oh, look at us.
离婚前的最后一个感恩节
Our last Thanksgiving as husband and wife.
你好
Hello.
嗨
Hi.
准备好去水族馆了吗?
Ready for the aquarium?
准备好了 为了缓解尴尬
I am. You know, and in an effort to reduce awkwardness
让我们知道如何以朋友身份相处 我打印了一张
as we learn how to function as friends, I printed out a list
礼貌对话的安全话题单
of safe topics for polite conversation.
这能让你更舒坦点就好
If that makes you more comfortable.
如果写一张能让我更舒坦的事情的列表
If there were a list of things that make me more comfortable,
写列表这件事肯定在那张表里
lists would be on the top of that list.
那开始吧... 噢
Okay, now... Oh.
"我们上次交谈过后 你养了什么宠物吗?"
"Since last we spoke, have you acquired any pets?"
没有 你呢?
No. You?
没有
No.
"我们上次交谈过后 你有计划
Um, "Since last we spoke, have you planned
或是去度过假吗?"
or gone on any vacations?"
我下周也许会去拜访我的阿姨
I might go visit my aunt next week.
在莫德斯托的那个?
Mm. Your aunt in Modesto?
不 在贝克斯菲尔德的那个
No, the one in Bakersfield.
贝克斯菲尔德 好吧
Bakersfield. I see.
我以前怎么没有这列表?
Where has this list been all my life?
我们需要你们帮忙洗盘子
We're gonna have you washing dishes.
围裙和手套在这边...就是...
Uh, aprons and rubber gloves are here... just...
刷一刷 冲干净 再叠起来
scrape, wash and stack.
有事的话 我随时都在
If you need me, I'll be around.
所以我们都不能上前面发食物吗?
So we don't even get to be up front where the action is?
有什么区别呢?
What difference does it make?
不知道 我还指望会有可怜的小孩
I don't know. I was hoping some poor kid
跑上前跟我说
would come up to me and say,
拜托您 先生 我还想要一点
Please, sir, I want some more.
你是在施食处
You're in a soup kitchen,
不是雾都孤儿的片场!
not a production of Oliver!
我又没有指望他们会唱歌
It's not like I'm expecting them to sing.
明天是73度
and then the next day was 73 degrees,
后天是72度
and the day after that was 72,
之后还是72度...
and then it was 72 again...
然后是74度
uh, then it was 74,
然后是今天...
and that brings us to today, at...
如果我有短裤我会穿的... 78度
I'd wear shorts if I had a pair... 78.
天气讨论完了吗?
Are we done discussing the weather?
这算是在"讨论"吗
I don't know if I'd call it "discussing."
你就坐在那儿 活都是我一个人干的
You kind of sat back and let me do all the work.
让我瞧瞧
Let's see
单子上下一条是什么
what's next on the list.
哦 是这个 呃 "你削木头吗
Oh, here. Uh, "Do you whittle,
削的话 你通常用什么
and if so, what kind of knife
- 样的..."  - Sheldon
- do you..."  - Sheldon.
我们已经认识很久了
We've known each other a long time.
我们完全有能力
We are perfectly capable of having a conversation
不依赖任何下载下来的清单对话
without relying on a list off the Internet.
好吧
All right.
那我们该聊些什么?
Well, what should we talk about?
不知道 想到什么问什么吧
I don't know. Just ask me whatever comes to mind.
好的
Very well.
我知道你已经在约会其他人了
I know you've been seeing other men.
你跟他们上床了吗
Have you had coitus with any of them?
天啊 我真是自找的啊
Man, I walked right into that one.
接下来要加一勺胡椒粉
Next we need a teaspoon of pepper,
我想 胡椒粉也是你小时候养的那条狗的名字
which, I believe, was also the name of your childhood dog.
好吧 你以为你懂很多是不是
Fine. You think you know so much.
辣妹里我最喜欢哪一个?
Who's my favorite Spice Girl?
- Baby  - 超级男孩里我最喜欢哪一个?
- Baby.  - Who's my favorite member of NSYNC?
- Justin  - 后街男孩里我最喜欢哪一个?
- Justin.  - Who's my favorite Backstreet Boy?
- 骗谁呢 超级男孩脑残粉  - 要命!
- Nice try. NSYNC forever.  - Damn it!
面对现实吧
Face it,
你难不倒我的... 我是老公中的战斗机
you can't stump me... I am the king of husbands.
我知道你不喜欢我在
I know that you don't like the lingerie
情人节给你买的那套贴身内衣
that I got you on Valentine's Day.
- 我知道你不喜欢"潮湿"这个词 我知道...  - 等等
- I know you hate the word "moist." I know...  - Hang on.
等等 我为什么我不喜欢你买给我的内衣?
Wait, wait. Why don't I like the lingerie you got me?
因为是橘色的
Because it's orange
你觉得这让你看上去像个放荡的胡萝卜
and you think it makes you look like a slutty carrot.
有意思
Interesting.
我从来没跟你说过
I never told you that.
- 你肯定说过  - 没有
- Sure you did.  - No.
我谁都没说过
I never told anyone that.
但是我写在日记里了
But I did write it in my journal.
什么?
What?
我都不知道你写日记
I didn't know you had a journal.
我还知道你说谎的时候音调会变高
I also know your voice gets higher when you're lying.
哪有啊
No, it doesn't.
这让我想起了高中生活
You know, this reminds me of high school.
你在餐厅工作吗?
You worked in a restaurant?
不 我在印度呢... 那里天气潮湿而且咖喱味十足
No, I was in India... it was humid and smelled funny.
好吧 我想我已经进入最佳状态了
All right, I think I'm getting into a groove here.
也没那么糟嘛
This isn't so bad.
还有5小时40分钟我们就能撤了
Only five hours and 40 minutes to go.
我们才干了20分钟?!
We've only been doing this 20 minutes?!
我之前读到过
You know, I read that
洗盘子是一种很好的冥想方式
washing dishes can be an excellent form of meditation.
秘诀在于洗盘子时
The key is that while washing the dishes
我们只能... 洗盘子
one should only be... washing the dishes.
你有口音
Just because you have that accent
并不意味着你说出来的东西就不蠢
doesn't mean what you say isn't stupid.
不 我是认真的
No, seriously.
说的是活在当下
It's about being present in the moment,
感受水的温热感
focusing on the feeling of the warm water,
洗涤剂的清香
the smell of the detergent,
盘子摩擦的声响 跟随自己的气息
the sound of the dishes squeaking, and following your own breath.
感受... 仅仅存在着的感觉
It's about... it's about simply being.
好的 我试一下
Okay.. I'll try  t.
我需要三个人来前台
I need three people out front.
- 我来!  - 我!  - 马上过去!
- I'll do it!  - Me!  - Right here!
不公平啊! 我刚刚在冥想!
No fair! I was meditating!
别生气嘛
Come on, don't be mad.
都多久以前的事了 而且是场意外
It was a long time ago, and it was an accident.
你怎么能意外读了我的日记?
How can reading my journal be an accident?
我不知道那是什么
I didn't even know what it was.
我看见在你床头柜上 就拿起来看一眼
I saw it on your nightstand. I picked it up.
你知道那是本日记的时候 为什么没有停下来?
Well, when you realized what it was, why didn't you stop?
你知道我这个人嘛 我是个书虫
You know me, I'm a big ol' bookworm.
好吧 我们先把饭煮完吧
All right. Let's just finish cooking.
好吧... 行 我来补偿你嘛
Well... Hey. O-Okay. Let me make this up to you.
我有时写网络日志
Sometimes I keep an online journal.
你来念我写的东西
I want you to read something that I wrote.
- 真的吗 我没事的  - 好吧
- Okay, really, I'm fine.  - Okay.
那就我读给你听
Well, then I'll read it to you.
是我们初遇的那天
It's from the day we first met.
- "真是美女啊 她叫Penny"  - 天啊
- "Beauty, thy name is Penny."  - Oh, God.
别念了
Stop.
我不要你念
I don't want you
这些拍马屁的话
to read something you think'll just butter me up.
我要你念最近写的东西
I want to hear the most recent thing you wrote.
好吧
Fine.
嗯...
Mmm...
"Penny是个大美女 就像我们的爱
"Penny's beauty, like our love,
与日俱增"
grows more with each passing day."
你真这么写的?
Does it really say that?
我说谎干嘛?
Why would I lie?
"老天 老天
"OMG. OMG.
新的星战马上要来了
We're so close to the new Star Wars.
简直受不了了
I can't take it.
噶"
Gah."
"噶"?
"Gah"?
你没读对
Well, you didn't read it right.
新的星战快来了 啊!
The new Star Wars is coming. Gah!
我感觉气氛有点尴尬
I'm sensing things have gotten awkward.
不 挺好的
No. It's okay.
要是朋友的话 就可以无话不谈
If we're friends, we should be able to talk about anything.
好吧
All right.
所以 你对我约会其他人有疑问
So, you had some questions about me seeing other people.
有一些
Just a few.
说吧
Go ahead.
你约会了几次?
How many dates have you been on?
都是些什么人? 你们去了哪?
Who were they with? Where'd you go?
你在哪遇见他们的? 你跟他们上床了吗?
Where did you meet them? Did you sleep with them?
离水族馆还有多久?
And how much longer to the aquarium?
我有点饿了
I'm getting kind of hungry.
我看看
Let's see.
我总共和3个人约会了6次
I have been on six dates with three different people.
不是喝咖啡就是吃饭
It was either for coffee or dinner.
一个在书店遇见的 还有两个是网友
One I met at a bookstore and two I met online.
没和谁睡
I haven't slept with anyone.
离水族馆还有40分钟
The aquarium is 40 minutes away.
在杂物箱里给你准备了
And there's a baggie of Cheerios for you
一包麦圈
in the glove compartment.
原味的还是蜜果味的?
Uh, regular or honey nut?
我把它们混在一起了
I mixed them.
混在一起了 怪不得男人们
You mixed them. No wonder gentleman callers
要把你家的门槛都踩烂了
are pounding down your door.
你有什么问题问我吗?
Do you have any questions for me?
就一个
Just one.
你还好吗?
Are you doing okay?
挺好的
I am.
嗯
Good.
我... 我希望你过得快乐
I... I want you to be happy.
我相信你
I believe you.
如果你放点麦片我会更相信你的
I'd believe you more if you threw a few Apple Jacks in here.
- 给你端过来了  - 多谢
- Here you go.  - Thanks.
一定是在逗我吧
You got to be kidding me.
你说什么
Sorry?
你... 你是Elon Musk
Y... You're Elon Musk.
是的
I am.
你在这儿做什么?
Wh... What are you doing here?
洗盘子啊
I'm washing dishes.
嗯...
Well,
我本来负责分发火鸡
I was on the turkey line, but I got demoted
但因为给了太多肉汁被下放到这里来了
for being too generous with the gravy.
我的天
Oh, man. I...
遇见你真是太荣幸了
What an honor to meet you.
我是特斯拉和SpaceX的忠实粉丝
I'm-I'm such a fan of Tesla and SpaceX.
(SpaceX是Elon Musk创立的美国太空运输公司)
都是你的公司
All your companies.
我是加州理工的Howard Wolowitz
Howard Wolowitz, Caltech.
很高兴认识你 Howard 来这里帮助不幸的人
Nice to meet you, Howard. Feels great to come down here
感觉不错吧?
and help the less fortunate, huh?
这还用你说?
Oh, yeah.
没什么比帮助别人更爽了
Nothing better than helping people.
这也是我在
Which is something I realized
国际空间站
when I was viewing Earth
遥望地球的时候意识到的
from the deck of the International Space Station,
我以卫星装备专家的身份在那儿工作了两个月
where I spent two months as a payload specialist, a job
毕竟哥是麻省理工培养的工程师啊
I was qualified for because I'm an MIT-trained engineer.
我还以为我添油加"汁"了呢
And I thought I ladled the gravy on thick.
对不起 只是...
Sorry. It's just...
你可是你啊
you're you, you know?
你能收养我就好了
And I really want you to adopt me.
你在感恩节的时候来这里
Well, you're here on Thanksgiving,
所以你大概也是个不错的人
so you're probably a good person.
我把我的妻子也带来了
Oh. I made my wife come down, too.
你觉得自己还会回到太空吗?
You think you might ever get back out to space?
这是份工作邀请吗? 因为我真的很想去火星啊
Is that a job offer? 'Cause I really want to go to Mars.
如果我能带上我老婆的话
Assuming I can bring my wife.
她不会占用太多空间的
She hardly takes up any room.
她基本可以随身携带
She's basically a carry-on.
我们还没做到那个地步
Well, we're not quite there yet,
但我们确实在找工程师
but we're always looking for engineers.
给你我的电子邮箱 我们保持联系
So let me give you my e-mail. We can stay in touch.
谢谢
Thank you.
看
Oh, look.
有人基本没动这份南瓜派呢
Someone hardly touched their pumpkin pie.
要和我分着吃吗?
Want to share it with me?
一个收容所剩下的
A-a partially eaten piece of pumpkin pie
半份南瓜派?
from a homeless shelter?
还是和Elon Musk分 必须的啊
With Elon Musk, you bet I do!
对于一个在水族馆餐厅的
You know, for a Thanksgiving buffet
感恩节自助餐来说 这可太差了
in an aquarium cafeteria, that was really bad.
你只是不爽他们发完了朝圣帽而已
You're just upset 'cause they ran out of Pilgrim hats.
他们给了那个小婴儿一个 他连眼睛都没睁开
They gave one to that baby. He wasn't even awake.
如果你没有对一个小婴儿不爽 这还不算假期呢
Well, it wouldn't be a holiday without you being mad at a baby.
噢
Oh.
想不想玩一个我发明的海洋主题游戏?
Would you care to play an ocean-themed game I invented?
好啊 怎么玩?
Sure. What is it?
这个游戏叫食物 朋友和对抗
It's called Food, Friend, Fight.
一个人选择三种水生生物
One of us chooses three aquatic creatures,
另一个人分别决定哪一个是食物
and the other one must decide which he would eat,
朋友或者敌人
befriend, or battle.
这就像亲吻 结婚和处决
So it's like Kiss, Marry, Kill.
那是什么?
What is that?
这个游戏给出三个人
It's a game where you're given three people
需要决定亲吻 结婚或者杀死的对象
and you choose which one you'd kiss, marry, or kill.
我的游戏好多了 比起结婚
Well, my game is better, 'cause instead of marrying someone,
你可以把他们吃掉
you get to eat them.
来玩吧
Let's just play.
我先给你来个简单的
I'll start you off easy.
电鳗 河豚 虾
Electric eel, pufferfish, shrimp.
额...
Hmm. Well,
我不会和一条电鳗打架
I wouldn't fight the eel, because I know
我知道它放出的电可是能杀死一匹马的
it can generate enough current to kill a horse.
所以我会吃掉鳗鱼
So I'd eat the eel,
和虾打一架 然后和河豚做朋友
fight the shrimp, and befriend the pufferfish,
毕竟在姐自大的日子里
because it would be nice to have company
有个陪伴也是极好的
on those days I feel bloated.
河豚会胀大身体
不错啊
Very well done.
谢谢
Thank you.
到你了
Okay, your turn.
海豹
Hmm. Seal,
八目鳗类鱼...
hagfish...
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants.
我想和海绵宝宝做朋友 但他不是真的
Well, I'd befriend SpongeBob but he's not real,
所以我不能那么做 是吧?
so I can't do that, can I?
但你能和八目鳗类鱼做朋友吗?
But you can pal around with a hagfish?
嘿 别逼我
Hey, let's not pull at that thread.
好吧 我和海绵宝宝打架
Okay. I'll fight SpongeBob,
因为他很友好 我们到最后最多只会互相挠痒痒而已
because he's so friendly we'll just end up tickling each other.
我和海豹做朋友
Um, I'll befriend the seal,
因为他能被训练 我现在的朋友
because he's trainable, which is the problem
可没这个优点
I'm having with my current friends.
这就意味着我要吃掉八目鳗类鱼了
Which means I'll have to eat the hagfish.
不恶心吗? 一条八目鳗类鱼
Isn't that gross? I mean, a hagfish can produce
瞬间就能制造一桶黏液哦
enough mucus to fill a bucket in a minute.
我知道 就当它自带肉汁吧 顺着食道就滑下去了
I know. It makes its own gravy... it'll slide right down.
我很怀念这个
I miss this.
你怎么能怀念一个自己从没玩过的游戏呢 傻吗?
How can you miss a game you've never played before, silly?
我想有时我是挺傻的
I guess sometimes I'm silly.
嘿 你去哪儿了? 我不知道这个火鸡烤熟了没有!
Hey. Where'd you go? I can't tell if the turkey's done!
来了!
Be right there!
嗨 宝贝儿
Hi, lover.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
对不起看了你的日记 我想补偿你
I'm sorry about the journal. I want to make it up to you.
我允许你在Facebook上发一张我的艳照
So I'm gonna let you post a shame photo of me on Facebook.
我偷看了老婆的日记 我是根调皮胡萝卜
我才不要把这个放到网上
I am not putting that on the Internet!
我不希望别人看到这个
I don't want people to see this.
连我都不想看到!
I don't want to see it!
不想别人看到啥?
Don't want people to see what, huh?
来点这个?
A little bit of this? Oh...
啊?
Huh?
再来点这个?
Some of this?
既然这是感恩节
And, since it's Thanksgiving,
再来点这个怎么样啊?
an extra helping of this?
感恩节快... 我去
Happy Thanks... Yikes.
我很高兴你和Amy相处的不错
I'm glad you had a nice time with Amy.
我也是 发现我和她
Me, too. It's comforting to know
能做朋友真是太舒心了
that she and I are able to function as friends.
我从没和前任当过朋友
Well, I've never been friends with any of my exes.
我相信你和Leonard可以的
Oh, I'm sure you and Leonard will be able to pull it off.
噢 是我的朋友Amy
Oh. It's my friend Amy.
你好
Hello.
嗨 Sheldon
Hi, Sheldon.
我现在从我妈妈家里开车回家
I'm just driving home from my mother's.
过得愉快吗?
Did you have a nice time?
是的
I did. Um...
今天早上和你一起我非常开心
listen, I really enjoyed spending this morning with you.
这也不全是我的功劳
Well, I can't take all the credit.
那只凤尾鱼方向游反了
It was pretty funny when that one anchovy
挺搞笑的
started going the wrong way.
是啊
It was.
听着
Uh, listen,
我在想
I... I was thinking that, um,
或许我准备好重新当你女朋友了
maybe I'm ready to be your girlfriend again.
噢
Oh.
我以为我们只是朋友
I thought we were just friends.
我们是
We are.
但我希望
But I was hoping,
- 或许...  - Amy
- maybe...  - Amy,
我擅长很多事情
I excel at many things,
但是放下你绝对不是我的强项
but getting over you wasn't one of them.
我想只做你的朋友就好了
I think I need to just be your friend.
好吧
Okay.
我理解
I understand.
嗯
Good.
我看了一个关于
Oh, I watched a video
八目鳗类鱼制造黏液的视频
of the hagfish producing mucus,
我决定改变主意 吃掉海绵宝宝
so I'm gonna change my answer and eat SpongeBob.
好的
Okay. Sure.